like said welcome brothers and sisters
to another Wednesday question and answer
will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God commanded the
world of keep brother
tanzel and God spake all these words
saying I am the Lord thy God which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt
out of the house of Bonet thou shall
have no other gods before me thou shall
not make unto thee any Graven image or
any likeness of anything that is in
heaven above or that is in the earth
beneath which that is in the water under
the Earth thou shall not bow down
thyself to them nor serve them for the
Lord thy God am a jealous God visiting
the iniquities of the fathers upon the
children until the third and fourth
generation of them that hate me and
showing Mercy unto thousands of them
that love me and keep my Commandments
thou shall not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain for the Lord will not
hold him Guiltless that taketh his name
in vain remember the Sabbath day to keep
it holy six day shall thou labor and do
all thy work but the seventh day is the
Sabbath of the Lord thy God in it thou
shall not do any work thou nor thy son
nor thy daughter thy man servant nor thy
maid servant nor thy cattle nor thy
stranger th that's that is within thy
gates for in six days the Lord made
Heaven and Earth the sea and all that in
them is and rested to Seventh Day
wherefore the Lord blessed the Sabbath
day and hollowed it honor thy father and
thy mother mother that thy days may be
long upon the land which the Lord thy
God giveth thee thou shall not kill thou
shall not commit adultery thou shall not
steal thou sh not bear false witness
against thy neighbor thou sh not cover
thy neighbor's house thou shall not
cover thy neighbor's wife nor his man
servant nor his maid servant nor his Ox
nor his ass nor anything that is thy
neighbors ReRe Exodus 21-17 and may the
Lord have a blessing to the reading of
his words in Jesus name we pray amen
amen
amen amen Tel you coming on view with
us uh yeah having a little uh technical
difficulties okay so here on question
and answer you can ask us a question and
we'll answer it according to the King
James Bible and if we cannot find the
answer we will seek further counsel to
bring you an answer at a later time now
the questions that we will not answer
are the vague and long scripture
questions and questions of debate we are
not here to debate but we are here to
spread the true Gospel of God so please
be as direct as possible with your
questions so we can be as direct as
possible with our answers out of the
King James Bible no other Bibles or book
will be acknowledged on this program
this is a live stream so feel free to
send in your questions that pertain to
Everlasting in life we just asking that
you keep your scriptures to a two
scripture maximum but let me introduce
you the family that's on the panel this
evening we got brother
Jerome Grace in peace Brother Julius
good evening everybody brother Dre good
evening brother tanzel good evening
everyone sister
Deborah good evening brother Sean good
evening and I'm brother
sister Deborah let us begin with our
first question of the evening uh yes
there are several held over questions
that will be answered first before
getting into tonight's
Q&A uh MC
ask when someone dies do they become an
angel when someone dies do they become
an angel well this is actually a
two-part question so let's first handle
when someone dies so let's go in there
Genesis 3 Genesis the 3
chapter Genesis the thir
chapter and when you get there let's
pick it up at that verse 12 because this
is after man and woman had sinned and
they were always blaming somebody else
and it brought death on the table but
read that Genesis 312 and 13 then we go
to skip go ahead
and the man said the woman whom thou
gavest to be with me she gave me of the
tree and I did eat blaming the wife go
ahead and the Lord God said unto the
woman what is this that thou has done
and the woman said the serpent begal me
and I did eat blaming the serpent should
have stayed away from him so this is
when the Lord put death on the table
skip down to verse 19 and let's see what
happens when someone dies go ahead and
the the sweat of thy face shall thou eat
bread till thou return unto the ground
for out of it was thou taken for dust
thou are and unto dust shall thou return
so no when someone dies they return into
the dust of the ground and they wait
there until the Lord calls them out of
the ground or out of the Grave so and
then the second one do they become an
angel let's go into Ezekiel 10 right
quick Ezekiel the 10th chapter because
if you understand the appearance of an
Angel then you would understand that no
and does not become an angel angels are
ministering Spirits sent forth to
minister to those that shall be Heirs of
Salvation Ezekiel 10 and when you get
there brother pick it up at that verse
14 and 15 let's see a little bit of what
the angels look like go
ahead and everyone have four faces and
the first face was the face of a chariot
and the second face was the face of a
man and the third the face of a lion and
the fourth the face of an eagle uhhuh
and the CH rooms were lifted up this is
the living creature that I saw by the
river of shebar so we see that these
angels here had four faces and we know
that man does not become a four-faced
creature he comes back just as he was
before he went into that ground except
he have a spiritual change but whatever
you look like now that's what you're
going to look like but let's go on
Genesis one and see what image will
we've taken on let's go in there Genesis
1 and read verse one and then we go skip
down go ahead in the beginning God
created the heavens and the Earth so
this is God creating the Heaven and the
Earth and let's see what man looks like
because he he doesn't look like an angel
in that aspect go ahead skip down to
verse uh 26 and 27 go ahead and God said
let us make man in our image after our
likeness and let us have dominion over
the fish of the sea and over the fowls
of the air and over the cattle and over
all the Earth and over every creeping
thing that creepeth upon the Earth so
when we see one another we can kind of
have an idea of what it is that God
presence is like because he's going to
tell us in 27 read so God created man in
his own image in the image of God
created he him male and female created
he them so we're created in the image of
God and we're created after his likeness
and we're not created in the image or
likeness of an Angel so no when man dies
when someone dies they go to the ground
and return until the Lord call them out
and then they come out looking like the
man that they went in only with a
spiritual change that's all I
get all right we hope that answered your
question as we move on to our
next next one Norman Nicks says my
friend says Genesis 1 verse2 is all the
scripture needed to prove God the Holy
Spirit I gave her Luke 1 verse 9
19 first John 5 verse 7 and Revelation 1
verses one two and three as drop the my
scripts are there other scripts she
can't she can't
argue all right so brother Julius if you
can assist with dropping the mic all
right first of all uh Genesis 1 and2
let's go to Genesis 1 and two let's go
through this uh quickly as we can
brother tenzel Genesis 1
and2 uh and let's see what it says first
of all
um that is a trinitarian teaching God
the Father God the son and God the holy
ghost that is not biblical only two of
are have the title of God that is the
father and that is the son they share
the title
God they share a title Lord but Genesis
let's go to Genesis 1 and let's look at
verse two when you get it because uh and
as a side note we strongly
suggest that all of us watch and rewatch
The Israel of God's production of the
spirit of God in his many forms the
spirit of God in his many forms so you
could rightly discern what scripture and
what context belong to what being all
right let's go and let's look at this
Genesis 1 and verse2 read the
scripture and the Earth was without form
and void and darkness was upon the face
of the deep and the spirit of God moved
upon the face of the waters it didn't it
did not say God the uh uh it didn't say
God moved upon the face of the waters it
said the spirit of God which is his
Angel so this is an Angel that's moving
on upon the face of the waters in this
context here what's the next scripture
let's go to what's the next scripture uh
Luke 1 verse 19 let's go to Luke 1 and
19 and this time this is an angel but we
gonna put a name to it this is this
Angel is not God the Holy
Spirit Luke 1 and
19 when you get it tzel read it because
a this is the a message from the angel
to John the Baptist
parents Luke 1:9 read it brother and the
angels answering said unto him I am
Gabriel that stand in the presence of
God and go ahead and am sent to speak
unto thee and to show these these Glad
Tidings now this is the Holy Spirit and
he says I am Gabriel that stand in the
presence of God on your own we can show
you that more perfectly from Isaiah's
point of view but let's go to Hebrews
chapter
1 Hebrews chapter
1 and we gonna pick this up at verse
six Hebrews chapter
1 and let's let's read verse
5 remember God the Father God the son
and God the Holy Ghost
is a trinitarian teaching it is not
biblical go ahead angels are not God
even though uh sday adven want to make
Michael Jesus uhuh go ahead at verse
Five For unto which of the Angels said
he at any time Thou Art my son this day
have I begotten thee and again I will be
to him a father and he shall be to me a
son he never said it to any of the
Angels sit down my right hand he never
said that go
ahead my uh verse six go ahead and again
when he bringeth in the first begotten
into the world he said and let all the
angels of God worship him so you got
Jesus that all the Angels whether they
are holy or Unholy they work for God go
ahead and are the Angels he said who
maketh his Angel spirit and his
ministers a flame of
fire and there so angels are Spirit
beings go ahead at verse eight but un to
the son he says thy Throne oh God is
forever and ever so he called so God
called the son God go ahead acep of
righteousness is the secep of thy
kingdom now verse
13 but to which of the Angels said he at
any time sit on my right hand until I
make thy enemies thy foot stol he never
said that so if the Holy Spirit or if
the holy spirit is God Jesus said at the
right hand of the father how come the
Holy Spirit don't sit at his left hand
never said that my last place Psalm
110 Psalm
110 we have a more sure word of Prophecy
remember what we just read he said unto
the son oh God sit down at my right hand
right Psalm 110 And1 Tel go ahead and
read it the Lord said unto my Lord sit
thou at my right hand until I make thy
enemies thy foot stol so we just read
that so there's only two that occupy the
title of God that is the father and the
son the holy spirit is his messenger
that stands in the presence of God and
the her last scripture Revelation
one Revelation
one the person who asked the question
Revelation one and one it's the same
thing in 1 John 5:7 that said there are
three that bear record In Heaven There
are three that bear record in heaven the
Father the Son and and the word which is
the Son and the Holy Ghost which stand
the angels of his presence Revelation 1
and one go ahead the revelation of Jesus
Christ that's
one which God God gave unto him that's
two to show unto his servants things
which must shortly come to pass and he
sent and signified it by his Angel unto
his servant John go
ahead who bear record of the word of God
and of the testimony of Jesus Christ and
of all things that he saw so
now there's no such thing as God the
Father God the son and God the Holy
Ghost it is the father and the son and
the ministering Spirit or the holy
spirit that stands in the presence of of
God who received the message from the
Father the father gives it to the Son
and the son gives it to the Angel and
the angel gives it to man and that man
was John who bear record and as well as
all the prophets so again watch the
lesson the Israel of God presentation of
the spirit of God and his many forms and
you'll have so much of a better
understanding that's all I got
Cornel all right thank you for that
brother you did assist in helping them
to drop the mic all right we're going to
move on to our next question
question next question Barbara still
says the question about the person not
being baptized before Jesus come will he
be baptized in the
wilderness what if that person was not
old enough to be baptized in the Israel
of
God right brother
Jerome well well you got the instance of
um people that's going to be in the
wilderness during the Great
Tribulation if they be blessed to make
it in there to be in the wilderness uh
during the Great Tribulation um you got
a uh a passage in Isaiah the 35th
chapter that kind of talk about that and
you also got some people that's going to
be gathered in the wilderness um when
the Lord return you know you going to
have a uh uh people that's going to be
gathered Israelites that's going to be
gathered all over the world they going
to be in that same Wilderness now the
question is about uh if they not
baptized will they get baptized um in
the wilderness well let's let's go read
something in Isaiah 35 and we gonna do
Ezekiel 20 also
uh
tanel
okay Ezekiel 35 pick it up at verse one
and we going to skip vers one Isaiah 35
or eek
Isaiah uh Isaiah 35 we going to do
Ezekiel afterwards but let's go to
Isaiah 35 and pick it up at verse one
then we gonna
skip okay Isaiah 35 verse one the
Wilderness and the solitary Place shall
be glad for them and the desert shall
rejoice and Blossom as the
RADS go ahead and read that too go ahead
and read that too and it's your blossom
abundantly and rejoice even with joy and
singing The Glory of lebano shall be
given unto it the Excellency of Carmel
and Sharon they shall see the glory of
the Lord and the eany of our God skip
down to verse eight and read to the
10 and a highway shall be there and a
way and it shall be called the way of
Holiness the unclean shall not pass over
it but it shall be for those the
wayfaring men though fool shall not he
therein no lion shall be there no any
rious Beast shall go up there on it
shall not be found there but the
redeemed shall walk
there and The Ransom of the Lord shall
return and come to Zion with songs and
everlasting Joy upon their heads they
shall obtain joy and gladness and sorrow
and singing shall flee away okay so it
said in verse 9 and 10 it said the
redeemed shall walk there they the ones
going to be in that Wilderness during
the Great Tribulation waiting on the
Lord to come when that seven trumpet
blow and he said the
ransom they gonna be there cuz they
going to be the on that's going to uh uh
return all right that got something to
do with Israel being gathered from all
over the world okay all right so now
they got to be brought under the bond of
the Covenant and part of being brought
under the bond of the Covenant is you
got to be baptized if you ain't already
baptized right okay and so and even the
ones that flee into that wildness if
they gonna be the ransom and the
redeemed they need to be baptized if
they ain't baptized
okay but for sure those that are going
to be gathered after the Lord come to
that same Wilderness if they ain't
baptized they got to be brought under
the bond under the Covenant and get
baptized or else he going to purge if
they don't want to do it okay so now
let's go to Ezekiel the 20th
chapter and read verse 34 through
38 yeah say sorrow and sign shall flee
away that's
right okay verse
34-38 okay Ezekiel 20 verse 34
and I will
bring and I will bring you out from the
people will gather you out of the
countries wherein ye are scattered with
the mighty hand and with the stretched
out arm and with Fury poured out I will
bring you into the Wilderness of the
people and there will I plead with you
face to face like I pleaded with your
fathers in the wilderness of the land of
Egypt so would I plead with you sayth
the Lord God and I will cause you to
pass under the rod and I will bring you
you into the bond of the Covenant and I
will Purge out from among you the rebels
and them that transgress against me and
I will bring them forth out of the
country wherein they sourn and they
shall not enter into the land of Israel
and ye shall know that I am the lord
well these people that's gathered to
this werness they GNA get an opportunity
to be brought under the bond of the
Covenant and I advise they go ahead and
do what it take to get brought under the
bond of the Covenant and baptism is one
of one of the things that got to be done
so that's all I got on that if anybody
want to add something yeah you know
Jerome that that uh Galatians 3 and 27
say for as many of you as have been
baptized into Christ have put on Christ
so like you say brother it's a must
needs isn't it yes sir all right thank
you for that brother hope that answered
their question as we move on to our next
next question look Mama Hayden
says in Psalms 100 vers 1 it says to
praise the Lord with a Joyful Noise can
that include praise dance or is that
against what is called praise and
worship on the Sabbath day all right
brother Jerome can you help out little
mama Hayes well let's go to that um
Psalms 100 verse
one and when you get it go ahead and
read psalms 101 verse one Psalms
100 verse one Psalms 100 verse one Make
a Joyful Noise unto the Lord All Ye
Lands and
serve just the first verse yeah it said
Make a Joyful Noise unto the Lord All Ye
Lands so I don't know what translation
you were reading out that
says praise the Lord with a Joyful Noise
but uh at any rate
um if you if it talks about praise
dancing in this
question you
know David he he did some praise dancing
but he had some understanding on who he
was praising for one thing he was
praising the god of Abraham Isaac and
Jacob we know him to be Jesus right uh
but a lot of people in the Sunday
churches what they call praise dancing
the Lord ain't quite pleased with that
praise and I'm G give you an example why
I say that okay so let's go to uh Mark
the 7th chapter
and we gonna pick it up at verse six
read it to the
nine brother
10 and he answered and said unto them
well have Isaiah prophesies of you
Hypocrites as it is written these people
honor me with their lips but their heart
is far from me how be it in vain do they
worship me teaching for Doctrine the
Commandments of men MH but laying aside
the Commandments of God ye hold the
tradition of men as the Washings of pots
and cups and many other such like things
ye do and he said unto them for well ye
reject the Commandments of God that ye
may keep your own tradition yeah so one
key thing is he said you worshiping me
in vain because you set my Commandments
aside but you still giving them praise
he not really pleased with that praise
you doing praise dancing but you
constantly rejecting the uh the truth of
the word of God he not pleased with your
praise be it dancing whatever okay now
often times like I said when when when
Sunday
Christians be calling theyel praise
dancing are are they giving God the
glory or are they getting the glory
often times it ain't God that's getting
the glory mainly because of what we just
read right
that that's all I got on me and and uh
in addition to that Brothers uh that's
Psalm 100 and verse one and verse two
how did you make a Joyful Noise unto the
Lord he said come before his presence
with
singing you know you singing You're
clapping and everything you know I see
the answer right there yeah to the true
and living God there you go because
Bible talks about another Jesus and
that's the one I was telling you about
Lord ain't play pleased when you
praising that Jesus right right yeah and
like you say too Jerome you got to have
a reason to sing and praise because I
know Miriam and all the women after the
Lord freed them out of Egypt they all
had timberl and singing and dancing they
had a reason to be happy and
joyful because it definitely Lord want
the praise he want that praise but you
got to understand who you giving the
praise to is it the real Jesus of this
Bible or is it that other one the one
Paul warning you about to stay away from
that's all I got on all right I hope
that answered your question is we move
on to our next one next one a h ask is
it a sin to lust after your own
wife brother Dre what you say about
lusting after your own wife is it a sin
to lust after your own wife well lust is
a strong intense
desire that for usually some something
that you don't have but you got a wife
is it a sin to lust and desire your wife
so if you desire your wife is that a sin
let's go to Proverbs the fth chapter
Proverbs
5 Proverbs the 5th chapter and we are
going to pick it up
at
uh Verse
18 verse 18
Proverbs 5 and8 tanel when you get it go
ahead let thy Fountain be blessed and
rejoice with the wife of thy
youth let her be as a loving Hind and
pleasant robe and let her breast satisfy
thee at all times and be thou ravish
always with her love sound like if you
ravish with her love you got a strong
desire for this woman and it ain't
nothing wrong with it in fact it's
saying
do that this is where the problem comes
in at though verse 20 go ahead and why
would thou my son be ravished with
strange women and embrace the bosoms of
a stranger uhhuh for the ways of man are
before the eyes of the Lord and He pth
all his going so when it comes to your
wife you should have a strong desire for
her you know I don't know that the word
lust necessarily is is one thing but
let's go to 1 Corinthians 7 Now 1
Corinthians 7 we're going to look at one
thing here 1 Corinthians
7 and verse five I mean no 1 Corinthians
7 and 3 go ahead brother let the husband
Render unto the wife due belov
benevolence and likewise also the wife
unto the husband skip down to verse
five def ye not one other except it be
with consent for a time that you may
give yourselves to fasting in prayer and
come together again that Satan tempt you
not for your inconsistency so it says
don't defraud ye one another you know
except it be with consent for a time and
the consent is to give yourself over to
fasting and prayer and during that time
like on the Sabbath day you're not
lusting after her and letting her you
know satisfy you at all times because
the time that you are giving to the
Lord but yeah nothing wrong with you
having a strong desire for your wife and
a man should with that that's it all
right thank you for that brother as we
move on to our next question next
question leaping lamb ask what is the
difference between God's laws and God's
Comm
Commandments What is the difference
between God's laws and his Commandments
brother Julius very little
difference very very little difference
they both are God's laws and notice they
are both given by God the Commandments
and
the which is the laws the same thing
they both are rules that mandate and
govern people they're both uh giving
people charges and they both have a
blessings and
penalties let's go to Psalm 19 let's
answer this
quickly let's look at what David
wrote Because the what's wrong with the
Ten Commandments they are laws that
govern man that govern the whole
world and a commandment is an order or a
precept the same
thing Psalm 19 let's read vers
7 10 and look at what they both or they
both ordained and and established Psalm
19 and verse 7 we gonna get these words
in here go
ahead the law of the Lord is perfect
converting the soul the testimony of the
Lord is sure making wise the
simple the statute of the Lord are right
rejoicing the heart the Commandment of
the Lord is pure
enlightening the eyes so we got the law
and the Commandments here in verse seven
and we got verse eight but they both
look what both of them do verse
11 moreover by them is thy servant warn
moreover by what by them the laws and
the Commandments same thing moreover by
them is what thy servant warant and
what's the reward and in keeping of them
there's great reward
hey break the law that's that's the
difference between the saint and The
Sinner is the law difference between
people in jail out of jail is the law
both have rewards both have penalties so
therefore moreover by them is thy
servant Warn and in keeping of them is
great
reward so the laws and the Commandments
same thing biblically speaking they the
same
thing all right thank you for that
brother hope that answer question as we
move on to our next next question
Stephen gugus says in Matthew 27 verse 9
was this a typo where it said to be
written by Jeremy Jeremiah the prophet
when it was prophesized by Zechariah in
Zechariah 11
verse2 all right Jeremy Jeremiah brother
Jerome what you got let's go read it
Matthews 27 excuse me verse
9 then was fulfilled that which was
spoken by Jeremy the prophet saying and
they took the 30 pieces of silver the
price of him that was value whom they of
the children of Israel did
value okay no that's not a
typo it was spoken um by
Jeremiah which is what it said in the
verse but it was actually
written by
Zariah let's go read it where Zariah
wrote it even though Jeremiah spoke it
okay Zechariah the 11th chapter verse 12
and
13 get it go ahead 12 and
13 and I said unto them if you think
good
give me my price and if not
forbear so they weigh for my price 30
pieces of silver and the Lord said unto
me cast it into the Potter a goodly
price that I was
priced at of them and I took the 30
pieces of silver and cast them to the
Potter in the house of the Lord yeah
that's all I got him all right brother
Jerome what a cheap price to pray for
somebody that did so much for us
30 pieces of silver man all right hope
that answered your question as we move
on to our next next question Robin Brown
says why is celebrating birthdays under
question now I celebrate because God
gave me and my loved ones another year
to get right not that day is special for
them to do as they please
all right so why celebrating birthday is
under question now because somebody went
into the Bible and pulled out two
examples and tried to put something bad
on you having a birthday but last time I
checked every time you get another 365
days from one year to the next it's a
blessing that's right let's go into that
uh Genesis the 40th chapter let's see
what Pharaoh did this is why they have
tried to make celebrating birthday
something that's not good or put it
under this question Jeremiah 40 when you
get there pick it up at that verse read
19 and 20 for me go ahead Jeremiah 409
and 20
yep say Jeremiah
40 19 and
20 uh
I'm sorry Genesis I'm sorry Genesis 40
Genesis 4019 and
20 Genesis
409 and
20 let's go and see what Pharaoh did
here this is one of the reasons they try
and put a blackout on birthday go ahead
yet within three days your Pharaoh lift
up thy head from off thee and shall hang
thee on the tree and the bird shall eat
thy flesh from off
so this is Joseph here letting his chief
Baker know that hey in three days
pharaoh go hang you and the Birds Go
come along and eat the flesh off of thee
verse 20 and it came to pass the third
day which was Pharaoh's birthday that he
made a feast unto all his servants and
he lifted up his head of the chief
Butler and of the chief Baker among his
servants skip down read
22 but he hung but he hang the chief
Baker As Joseph had interpreted to them
so because Pharaoh did this on his
birthday and he hanged the chief Baker
this is one of the reason that they say
you know that you should not be
celebrating your birthday now let's go
over to um Matthew the 14th chapter
Matthew
14 because to have a a birthday is a
blessing I'm sure uh methusa appreciated
all 969 of his
Matthew the 14th
chapter and when you get there pick it
up at that verse six Matthew 14 and6 go
ahead but when herod's birthday was kept
the daughter of the herodes dance before
them and pleased Herod now this is John
the Baptist here when they gonna when um
herod's going to make sure John the
Baptist is
beheaded on his birthday go ahead
whereupon he promised with an oath to
give her whatsoever she would ask and
she being before instructed of her
mother said give me here John the
Baptist head in a
charger and the King was sorry
nevertheless for The Oak's sake and then
which sat with him at meat he commanded
it to be given her so because he told a
I give you whatever you want and uh she
wanted John the Baptist head in the
charger he went and had John beheaded
verse 10 and he sent and beheaded John
in the
prison go ahead and his head was brought
in a charger and given to the damsel and
she brought it to her
mother his disciples came and took up
the body and buried it and went and told
Jesus yep so they beheaded John the
Baptist Herod did this on his birthday
so this is why people are trying to put
a black eye on someone having a birthday
birthday now the Lord say our time is
always it's a blessing to have another
birthday but it doesn't give you a right
to go out and sin on your birthday so
you keep all the laws of God and you'll
be okay if you want to do a little
appreciation on your
birthday in addition to that brother
Cornel if I may if I may be allowed
there was a question came in last week
and I answered the question and my
response was not to challenge birthdays
but to show that the Bible in the Bible
birthdays are
mentioned that's
correct so nothing questioning the
birthdays just showing you that the
Bible show you a couple of examples
where birthdays are acknowledged that's
it right okay hope that answers your
question as we move on to our next I'm
moving on to the next one another
question from Barbara
uh her question is related from last
week uh question which is talking about
halah and that question was are we able
to eat
Hala fit to eat or use According to
Islamic law meat and it gives beef bacon
or lamb so her question is
is he saying we can't eat beef
bacon all right brother Dre what you say
no sister I am not saying we can't eat
beef bacon I was simply making a note of
what Hal is and what the process is and
according to their dietary law they have
things in it that are
unclean that we should not eat we go by
the dietary law and under the dietary
law we can eat beef bacon so let's go
over to uh Leviticus 11 and we gonna
read verse three Leviticus 11 and
three tanzel when you get it go ahead
and read
it whatsoever part of the hook and is
clothing for it and cheth the Cur among
the Beast that ye shall eat that's right
so
cows you know have split hoodes and they
chew the cud they are clean to eat and
that is where beef bacon comes from so
yes we can eat beef bacon let's go and
read one more passage let's go to
Deuteronomy 14 and Deuteronomy 14 and
verse 6 when you get it go ahead
brother and every Beast that parth the
hoof and cleaveth the cliff in to two
Claws and cheth the cud among the Beast
that ye shall eat that shall eat so the
cow does that and it is clean for us to
eat so sister if you want to fry you
some beef bacon in the morning have at
it that's all I got that's right yes sir
hope that ansed your question as we
continue to move on to our next one our
next question JoJo asks should I sign
divorce
papers hey based on those five words in
that question let's go to Philippians 4
Philippians the 4th chapter Philippians
the 4th chapter should I sign divorce
papers Philippians 4 and read verse 6
and seven
go ahead be careful for nothing but in
everything by prayer and supplication
with Thanksgiving let your request be
made known unto God so be careful for
nothing let your request be made known
to God what it is that's on your heart
and what it is you thinking about and
your intents and verse seven go ahead
and the peace of God which Pass of All
understanding shall keep your hearts and
Minds through Christ Jesus and
so that's all I got on
that hope that answered your question as
we move on to our next one next question
laa Dallas
says in Ezekiel 8 vers 15-
17 why do we face the East when we pray
if it was in an
Abomination can you explain this H an
Abomination I didn't read that but
brother Jerome what you
got no it's not
Abomination to face the East it's an
Abomination to worship the sun whether
it's in the east north south or east or
west that's
right and that's what they were doing
they were worshiping the Sun at the time
it came up in the
East okay but you got a lot of people
worshiping the Sun and it's in the west
so it's that's the Abomination
worshiping the sun okay so let's go to
Deuteronomy the 4th
chapter and read verse 16 through
19 Deuteronomy
yeah verse 16 through
19 what was we going to read Ezekiel or
no excuse me uh we
can yeah let's let's do that I shouldn't
I should have read it Ezekiel the 8th
chapter verse 15 through
17 then say he unto meast thou seen this
oh son of man turn thee yet again and
thou shalt see greater Abomination than
these and he brought me into the inner
Court of the Lord's House and behold at
the door of the Temple of the Lord
between the porch and the altar were
about five and 20 men with their backs
towards the Temple of the Lord and their
faces towards the east and they
worshiped the son towards the east then
he said unto meast thou seen this oh son
of man it is a light thing to the house
of Judah that they commit the
Abominations which they commit here they
have filled the land with violence and
have returned to provoke me to anger and
lo they put the bran to their
nose yeah so yeah that's what they was
doing they worshiping the son that
happened to be towards the east they
mean they did was doing it early because
that's when the sun is in the East when
it's early okay uh I don't know exactly
where I know it's in the Chronicles
where Solomon prayed towards the
temp say that again it's in 2 Chronicles
6 and 26 as well as first K 8 and
2535 yeah and so it show where you know
Solomon you know he asked the Lord if
you hear they prayer if we face towards
thy house your temple you know would you
hear it and the Lord
said he would you know and so
uh there's times where people that's
living in other parts of the country
where facing the temple is actually west
of them and so they'll be praying toward
the
west you know so it ain't you praying
toward the East it's what you praying to
a worshiping you know and it was the son
the verse that you gave was they was
worshiping the Sun and that's the
abomination in the eyes of the Lord so
now let's go read that Deuteronomy
chapter 4 verse 16-9
you get it go ahead and read let you
corrupt yourselves and make you a Graven
image a similitude of any figure the
likeness of male or female the likeness
of any Beast that is on the earth the
likess of any Wing foul that flyth in
the air the likess of any thing that
creepeth on the ground the likeness of
any fish that is in the waters beneath
the
Earth and as thou lifted up thy eyes
unto heaven and when thou seest the sun
and the moon and the stars even all the
hosts of Heaven should us be driven to
worship them and serve them which the
Lord thy God have divided into all the
Nations under the whole heaven but the
Lord have taken you and brought you
forth out of the iron furnace even out
of Egypt to be unto him a people of
inheritance as ye are this day yeah so
that's the Abomination is the worship
been the Sun the moon or the stars or
whatever is in the heavens you know and
it don't matter if you facing the north
south and the East when you do it okay
it's an abomination of the Lord that's
all I got on hey bro Jerome can we go to
that uh scripture that Dre mentioned at
2 Chronicles 7 since they put the word
Abomination and it'll this is the Lord
speaking out his own eyes about why it
is that we Face the East that's 2
Chronicles 7 and um and that verse
14 15- 16 and then you can expound on
that when you get there brother tanzel
read that 2 Chronicles 7 and pick it up
um at that verse 14- 16 go ahead brother
if my people which I call by my name
shall humble themselves and pray and
seek my face and turn from their Wicked
Ways then will I hear from heaven and
will forgive their sin and will heal
their land now my eyes shall be open and
my ears attended unto the prayer that is
made this place for now have I Chosen
and Sanctified this house that my name
may be there forever and my eyes and my
heart shall be there
perpetually right you wrong yeah so
that's why they were praying they were
praying towards this holy place where
the Lord said I'mma place my name there
and that was and that was Jerusalem you
know so that's what was and the Lord
said he will hear that prayer yes all
right thank you for that brother hope
that answered that question as we move
on to our
next uh next question Glenn Sirius asked
in Jeremiah 25:
34-38 is the Lord speaking to Israel in
these verses and if so when was this
accomplished brother Julius let's go
there let's go go to that Ezekiel uh
let's go to uh I'm sorry let's go to
that that Jeremiah 25th
chapter yes it's to Israel but it's to
all the false prophets beginning from
Israel to everybody else who are
teaching the word of God falsely but
this time we're going to read something
we're g to start higher and then we're
gonna get into your scriptures so we
going to pick this up brother tanzel at
Jeremiah the 25th chapter cuz you got to
read the whole chapter and it's a yet
future thing this is when the Lord
returns Jeremiah 25 but the prophecy is
right here Jeremiah 25 we gonna read
vers 15- 17 go ahead but thus say the
Lord God of Israel unto me take the wine
cup of the Fury at my hand and cause all
the nations to whom I sent thee to drink
only Israel say all the nations all
Israel all all the nations go ahead and
they shall drink and be moved and be mad
because of the sword that I will send
among them go ahead then took I the cup
of the Lord's hand and made all the
nations to drink unto whom the Lord had
sent me get down to verse 32 let's
go thus say the Lord of hosts behold
evil shall go forth from Nations to
nations from Nation to Nation go ahead
and a great Whirlwind shall be raised up
from the coast of the Earth go ahead and
the slain of the Lord shall be at that
day from one end of the Earth even unto
the other end of the Earth they should
not be lamented neither gathered nor
buried they should be dung upon the
ground man go
ahead how ye Shepherds and cry and
wallow yourselves in the ashes ye
principles of the flock princi of the
flock from the from the bishop to the
Evangelist all the teachers and stuff
all the religious heads go ahead for the
days of your Slaughter and of your
dispersions are accomplished and ye
shall fall like a pleasant
vessel and the shepherd shall have no
way to flee nor the principle of the
flock to escape so all the religious
preachers should have no place to flee
when the Lord come because the book said
the ignation of the Lord is Against All
Nations that's Israel and all the other
people who are are besides Israel Israel
is just the cheap we the we are the
Lord's uh uh priest but the
Nations uh all this Catholicism and all
the branches of it that that done
misinterpret it and mistaught the word
of God this is the m for them when the
Lord come back skip down
uh but that's that's good enough and the
shepherd should have no way to nowh to
flee nor the principle of the flock to
escape this when and this is future and
this when the Lord come back he G to
execute judment upon all these false
prophets on your own when you want to
deal with Israel read Jeremiah the 23rd
chapter but this scripture is for
everybody that's right brother jul not
even the mountains and the Rocks still
be able to hide them from the Lord
yep all right thank you for that brother
as we move on to our next question our
next question Cass Lee uh says my
brother asked me will God get mad with
you if you pray too much I told him no
but can you provide me with the
scripture or scriptures that represents
the answer for this question all right
you told him no that hey because that's
up to each individual how much they want
to pray based on your needs your desires
and what it is you might be looking for
from the Lord so let's go into job n
right quick job n and then we leave
there brother we go go to first
Thessalonians 5 let's go to job nine
because he wants to know can you pray
too much and let's see what shape the
world is in and see if this should limit
your prayer job 9 and read that verse 24
for me when you get there brother the
Earth is given into the hand of the
wicked oh so if the Earth is given into
the hand of the wck wied it look like we
need to pray all the time man nonstop
let's go to first Thessalonians first
Thessalonians the fifth chapter 1
Thessalonians 5 and when you get there I
want you to pick it up at that verse uh
16 through 18 for
me first Thessalonians 5 yep pick it up
at verse 16 16 um
yeah go
ahead Rejoice ever more and pray without
ceasing oh pray without ceasing so
that's Lord saying hey nonstop you just
continue to pray go ahead and everything
give thanks for this is the will of God
in Christ Jesus concerning you yeah so
hey Lord say pray without ceasing so how
can we put a limit on praying let's go
to James the fth chapter James 5
and when you get there we're going to
pick it up at that verse 14 because the
way this world and the shape it's in we
need to pray all the
time James 5 when you get there pick it
up at that verse 14 go ahead because we
got a lot of sick we got Afflicted got
people that got some real issues out
here go ahead is any sick among you let
them call for the Elders of the church
and let them pray over him anoint him
with oil in the name of the Lord yes and
the prayer of faith shall save the SI
and the Lord shall raise him up and he
if he have committed sins they shall be
forgiven him uhhuh confess your false
one to another and pray one for another
that ye may be healed the effectual
fervent prayer of a righteous man
available much effectual fervent prayer
of a righteous man so when your prayers
are reaching the Throne of God hey you
should keep them going non-stop now
let's let's go into um Daniel the 6th
chapter Daniel 6 yes sir yes
sir great script let's see let's see how
often Daniel Prayed
here because nobody should be able to
limit the prayers that you want to send
up before God if you feel as though your
need is constant and you need help
Daniel 6 and read that verse 10 for me
go
ahead now when Daniel knew that the
writing was signed he went into his
house and his window being open in his
chamber towards Jerusalem he kneeled
upon his knee three times a day and
prayed and gave thanks before his God as
he did a four time so Daniel Prayed
three times a day and gave thanks unto
his God so if you want to put a prayer
in between those three times we can't
see where anything is wrong with that
one more place right quick let's go to
Luke 22 Luke to I just want to add that
uh towards Jerusalem piece that's in
that scripture there you go toward the
East yeah toward the East right okay yes
sir indeed good add on let's go to Luke
um at Luke 22 right quick Luke
22 and pick it up at verse and read 31
and 32 when you get there go
ahead and the Lord God and the Lord said
Simon Simon behold Satan have desired to
have have you that he may sift you as
sweet as weak but I have prayed for thee
that thy faith fail not and when thou
are converted strengthen thy brother
yeah skip down brother to that verse 36
for me go ahead then said he unto them
but now he that have a purse let him
take it and likewise his
script and Skip down verse 39 skip down
39 and read go ahead and he came out and
went as he as he was want to the
mountain of Olive and his disciples also
followed him and when he was at the
place he said unto them pray that he
entered not into temptation so Jesus
telling his disciples hey pray that he
entered not into temptation he didn't
say once or twice he just said pray go
ahead and he was withdrawn from them
about a stone cast and kneel down and
prayed saying father if thou be willing
remove this cup from me
nevertheless not my will but thine be
done yes and we can read what Jesus
prayed continually go ahead and there
appeared an angel unto him from Heaven
strengthening him and being in an Agony
he prayed more earnestly and his sweat
was as it were great drops of blood
falling down to the ground okay one more
ver and when he rose up from prayer and
was come to his disciples he them
sleeping for sorrow and he
said he said why sleepest ye rise up and
pray Les you enter into temptation so
can nobody put a limit on your prayer
when you feel the need Jesus hey when he
was in agony he prayed more earnestly he
prayed even harder to the father that's
right because he needed some help so let
nobody you know tell you that uh you
praying too much because a lot of people
don't pray enough
right all right that's all I got moving
on to the next question uh yes we are
now into tonight's Q&A for December the
25th
2024 sister Israel says I was talking to
someone at school and they say that God
is an
onent so they chant the word um or
arms for peace
or when they are stressed I know
chanting is wrong so is there any
Scripture saying so or how can I explain
that explain to her that it's wrong Jay
what you say first of all the thing is
that that they're telling you about
chanting on and that is in in to deal
with
Hindu Hinduism that's what that's about
and that is a god a strange God that is
no God at all but I um I'm looking at
something here is is it's a symbol of
Hinduism universe created with three
syllables which is a m and are to
represent the Trinity of three major
gods and it goes into all these gods
that they
worship this this noise is made toward
these Gods that's now let's go to the
scripture let's go to Exodus 23 Exodus
23 um and we're gonna read one verse
there verse 13 Exodus 23 and 13 go ahead
brother when you get it and in all
things that I have said unto you be
circum respect and make no mention of
the name of other gods neither let it be
heard out of thy mouth because that's
what get us in trouble we should have no
other gods before our God now let's go
over to Joshua 23rd chapter Joshua 23
and we gonna start at verse 6 Joshua 23
verse six when you get it go ahead
brother be ye therefore very correct
rageous to keep and to do all that is
written in the book of the law of Moses
that you turn that aside there from to
the right hand or to the left
yes that you come not among these
nations these that remain among you
neither make mention of the names of
their God nor cause to swear by them
neither serve them nor bow yourself unto
them so we shouldn't be chanting to know
God other than the God of Israel calling
on his name go ahead but cleave unto the
Lord your God as ye have done until this
day now let's go to First Peter 3 and we
gonna read verses 10 through 12 there 1
Peter 3 verses 10 through 12 and this
goes right along with what Cornell was
just talking about we should pray to the
Lord Our God if we going through
anything and he
Peter 3 pick it up at verse 10 and read
the 12 brother tanzel go ahead when you
get it but he that will love life and
see good days let him refrain his tongue
from evil and his lips that they speak
no
God let him asso evil and do good let
him seek peace and is Su it for the eyes
of the Lord are over the righteous and
his ears are open un their prayers but
the face of the Lord is against them
that do evil and it would be evil for us
to chant whatever this person is talking
about chanting because it is connected
to
Hinduism but the Lord's ears are open to
the prayers of the righteous that's
right pray to the Lord Our God not to
some Hindu god that's all
yes sir all right thank you for that
brother hope that answered that question
as we move on to our next one next
question TX doino says where can I go to
get more proof that we are the true
Israelites I I've read many history
books and a lot of what I've read leads
me to think so but I haven't fixed on a
definite yes yet would would would be a
blessing if you could point me to a
place I can
read all right well because we're very
limited for time but let's go to uh
Genesis 32 because the bloodline of
Abraham and then he had Isaac and then
Isaac had Jacob and then Jacob had 12
sons which made up to 12 tribes of
Israel but let's go to Genesis 32 and
let's see when the name Israel came into
play because the same Isaac that had
Jacob this is who we talking about here
Genesis 32 and when you get that brother
pick it up at that verse 24 and go
ahead and Jacob was left alone and there
Wrestled a man with them until the
breaking of the day and when he saw that
he prevailed not against him he touched
the hollow of his thigh and the hollow
of Jacob's thigh was out of joint as he
wrestled with
him said let me go for the day breaker
and he said I would not let thee go
except thou bless me he said unto him
what is thy name and he said Jacob and
he said thy name shall be called No More
Jacob but Israel for as a prince H has
thou power with God and with men so this
is when the Lord brought in the name
change and he told Jacob your name is
not Jacob no more but Israel which is
God's name so here we are with the
beginning of Jacob taking on the name of
God go to Amos 3 right quick Amos 3 Amos
the 3
chapter because the Lord chose him
bloodline to teach all the rest of the
Sons and Daughters of Adam no matter
what color they might be Amos 3 pick it
up verse one go ahead he chose one
family to teach the other families go
ahead hear this word that the Lord has
spoken against you oh children of Israel
against the whole family with which I
brought up from the land of Egypt
saying have I known of all the families
of the earth therefore I will punish you
for all your iniquities so the Lord is
talking to Israel here go ahead can two
walk together except they be agree no
they can't verse seven and eight go
ahead surely the Lord God would do
nothing but he reveal his secret unto
his servants the prophet yes the lion
have roared who will not fear the lord
God have spoken who can but prophesy and
the Lord chose Israel to prophesy his
word to all the rest of the sons of Adam
turn over to Romans nine right quick
Romans nine and let's pick it up at that
verse three there verse three and
Deuteronomy also will give you a whole
lot of
examples of Israel and how you able to
put your fing on them Deuteronomy I mean
Romans 9 and verse three go ahead I
could wish that myself were a curs from
Christ for my brethren my Kinsmen
according to the flesh uhhuh who are
Israelites to whom pertain the adoption
and the glory and the covenants and the
giving of the law and the service of God
and the promises uhhuh who are the
fathers and of whom as concerning the
flesh Christ came who is over all God
bless forever amen so it's the
Israelites that have the adoption of
glory and the covenants and the giving
of the law that the Lord wanted us to
share with everybody else and this Paul
that is speaking here he was a benjamite
out of the tribe of Benjamin that was
one of the sons of Jacob here and Christ
himself was an Israelite because he also
came through that bloodline there now
let's go quickly to um Isaiah 42 and
verse
22 Isaiah 42
and22 because we want you to understand
and come on board with who Israel is so
that you can turn your light on even
better Isaiah 42 and verse 22 what else
about Israel go ahead but this is a
people robbed and spoiled they are all
of them snared in holes and they are HID
in prison houses they are for a prey and
none deliver for a spoil and none say
restore so when you go to any prison we
stacked up in there we hid in prison
houses go ahead who among you will give
ear to this who will hearken and hear
for the times to come and who is it
that's go to hearken and here we hoping
that you have an ear to hear this and
why did the Lord stack Us in these
prison houses go ahead who gave Jacob
for a spoil and Israel to the robbers
did not the Lord
yeah he against whom we have sinned for
they would not walk in his ways neither
they were obedient unto his law so that
is the reason that the Lord has punished
us and sent us into the Four Corners at
Earth because we were the only family
that he knew and we refused to walk in
his word go to Deuteronomy 28 we'll read
a scripture or two and then that'll be
it and then we ask you to please tune in
to our black history which begins
February the 1 2025 at 12 noon and you
will get more proof of it
there as um Deuteronomy 28 and pick it
up at that verse 15 brother go
ahead 20 but it shall come to pass if
thou will noten to the voice of of the
Lord thy God to observe to do all his
Commandments and his statutes which I
command thee this day that all these
curses shall come upon thee and overtake
thee yeah skip down brother to verse 32
and go ahead this happened during
slavery here and before thy sons and thy
daughters go ahead verse 32 thy sons and
thy daughters shall be given unto
another people and thy eyes shall look
and fail with longing for them all the
day long and there shall be no might in
thy hand y so when they took our sons
and daughters away on the wagons to
other places you had no power in your
hand to do nothing this is Israel and
part of the punishment now skip down and
we'll read that verse 64 go
ahead and the Lord shall bring thee into
Egypt again with ships by the way
whereof I spake unto thee Thou shalt see
it no more again and there shall you be
sold unto your enemies for Bond men and
bond women and no man shall bu shall buy
you nobody else but Israel was brought
over here on ships and sold as male and
female slaves and nobody else can take
that credit for that everybody else came
in on a cruise ship or migrated but we
were brought over here as punishment
from not serving the lord that is Israel
anybody else yes please please read
verse 46 because this is the sign that
you looking at these conditions are
resting on Israel to this go ahead
brother
46 and they shall be upon thee for a
sign and for a wonder and upon thy seed
forever and that sign is on us you
cannot get around it so if
you all these things written in the
scriptures is the sign that speak to
your condition as a collective not
individual as a
collect we the
majority
we yeah that's true thank you for that
add-on brother and even at 61 right
quick tzel read
that
61 61
also every sickness and every plague
which is not written in this book of the
law them will the Lord bring upon thee
unto thou be destroyed brother we got a
lot of health issues
on lot of sickness stuff that don't even
have a cure for it and like brother Dre
is saying these things are put on us for
a sign so that no one else will be
mistaken for being
Israel it is us thank you for that
brother appreciate you sister Deborah
next question
next question Tracy bures asks when we
celebrate the New Year what day and
month does it start brother
Julius I never read in the Bible but the
Lord commanded us to celebrate a new
year the uh uh uh celebrate a new year I
can read what he told us in Leviticus
the 23rd chapter to keep his feast in
their Seasons let's go to deuteron the
16th
chapter remember the Lord said my ways
are not like your ways and my thoughts
like your thoughts man got his New Year
and God has his new year man's New Year
start January the 1 with Roman and God's
New Year start around the end of March
going into
April Deuteronomy 16 And1 let's look at
what the books say I'm sorry I'm sorry
Exodus 12 Exodus 12 Exodus 12 tzel my
apologies one and
two when you get it go ahead and the
Lord spake unto Moses and Aaron and the
land of Egypt saying this month shall be
unto you the beginning of months and it
shall be the first month of the year to
you now let's put a name on it
Deuteronomy 16 And1 cause Exodus 12
talks about the
Passover and unleavened bread in the
first month what's this month called
Deuteronomy and one when you get it read
it my brother observe the month of ABIA
and keep the Passover unto the Lord thy
God for in the month of Abe the Lord thy
God brought thee forth out of Egypt by
night like he told you in Exodus 12 the
month of first month is the month AB so
that's like March end March going into
April the Lord's time my last place
Esther 3 the Book of Esther the thir
chapter and just verse
seven still after Israel went into
captivity they still call it by the
Babylonian name but it's still the first
month of the
year Esther 3 and 7 when you get it go
ahead in the first month that is the
month Nissan in the 12th year of king of
hazar that's good enough brother that's
all I wanted to show you that Nissan ABB
is still the first month of the year
and we're talking around end of March
going into April the Lord's time that's
right yeah I've never read what the Lord
say celebrate the new year
right yeah our new year is when the
trees start the the bud and the flowers
are coming out of their hibernation
that's our new year yep things you can
see yes sir all right brother thank you
for that hope that answered their
question sister Deborah
yes next question She also asked is it
all right to start fasting on the
Sabbath day brother Dre what you say
yeah absolutely it's nothing wrong with
you fasting any day that you you choose
to fast except for feast day on those
days we are to have a feast and we
should eat but if you want to fast on a
regular weekly Sabbath day as long as
it's not fallen on the feast day that we
should have food to eat then absolutely
a fast is all good that's all I got all
right thank you for that brother moving
on to our next question moving on Gary
Sanderson says according to Revelations
21 verse1 the first Heaven and the first
Earth were passed away can you please
explain this TR transition if it's
literal or spiritual the scripture says
the Earth abided
forever all right brother
Jerome yeah let's go read that
Revelations
21 and verse one it is it is
literal Revelations 21 verse
one go
ahead and I saw a new Heaven and new
Earth for the first Heaven and the first
Earth were passed away and there was no
more
sea and there was no more SE so by the
time you get to this um time uh you'll
be into the father's Kingdom because in
the father's Kingdom it ain't going to
be no more seeds but let's read about
the Lord's Kingdom let's tie that
with chapter 20 verse 13
the SE these seeds we talking about this
is literal seeds all right and the
father's King Ain't goingon to be no
more seed that's literal all right but
in the son's Kingdom you'll still have
some seeds I just want to show you an
example of that read verse 13 and the
Sea gave up the dead which were in it
and death and Hell delivered up the dead
which were in them and they were judg
every man according to their works yeah
so whatever dead people died and was in
the Seas they the Seas gave him up
literal seeds okay now let's tie that
with Revelations chapter
6 these events that's going to literally
happen to the heavens and the Earth okay
Revelation chapter 6 verse
12-4 and I beheld when he had opened the
six seal and low there was a great
earthquake and the sun became black as
sack off of H
and the moon became as blood and the
stars of Heaven failed unto the Earth
even as a fig tree casteth her untimely
figs when she is shaken of A Mighty Wind
so other plac in the bible let you know
the sun and the moon gonna be
darkened okay go ahead and the heaven
departed at a scroll when it is rolled
together in every mountain and Island
were moved out of their places that's
going to literally happen go ahead and
the kings of the earth and the great men
and the rich men and the chief captains
and the Mighty Men And every Bond Man
and every free man hid themselves in the
dens and in the rocks of the mountains
uhuh and they said to the mountains and
rocks fall on us and hide us from the
face of him that sth on the throne and
from the Wrath of the lamb for that
great day of his wrath has come and who
shall be able to stand yeah and the
reason why they going to be asking for
the rocks and the mountains to follow on
when them R Heavens roll back literally
they going to literally see the Lord
they gonna know he ain't no joke he for
real
knocking uh Corel can I go to one U one
place also Psalm 104 because the the
person asked question said the Earth
abideth forever yes the Earth abideth
forever but look what the Lord do to the
Earth
yeah Psalm 104 and read verse
30 PSM
104 and verse 30 thou send forth thy
Spirit they are created and thou
renewest the face of the Earth thou
renewest the face of the Earth that's
all I got yeah thank you for that like
you told Adam that like you told Noah
son replenish the Earth yeah that's
right yeah all right hope that aned your
question next question yes move moving
on Mr and Mrs pores asked do we have any
videos on
Thanksgiving I need to know what
scriptures I can share with those
struggling why they should or shouldn't
observe
it now we don't have any videos on that
if you want to celebrate Thanksgiving
that's uh that's your choice if you
don't want to celebrate it that's your
choice and that is how we always answer
it here at um at the Israel of God and
it's up to you that's your choice that's
all I
got okay next question yes philosophy
asks when we pray is it only to the
father or can we pray to Jesus as
well well being that they both that
Jesus the son took on the father's name
Jesus but let's go and see what it says
here let's go into Matthew the 6th
chapter Matthew
6 and when you get there pick it up at
that verse
three so um read that verse three and
four and then we GNA skip down to read
six go ahead but when thou doest arms
let not thy left hand know what thy
right hand doeth uhhuh that thy arms may
be in secret and their father was seeth
secret himself shall reward thee openly
so this is Jesus he's in the flesh
telling us how to pray skip down to
verse
six but thou when thou prayest enter
into thy closet and when thou H has shut
thy door pray to thy father which is in
secret and thy father would see if
secret shall reward thee openly yes and
the father's name is Jesus because the
son came go to
Luke go to
Luke Luke 11 and pick it up at that one
when you get
there because this is a question that
the disciples asked Jesus here go ahead
and it came to pass that as he was
praying in a certain place when he he
ceased what if his disciples said unto
him Lord teach us to pray as John also
taught his
disciples and he said unto them when ye
pray say Our Father which are in heaven
Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom come
thy will be done as in heaven so in
Earth so he was telling us to pray into
the father who we know his name is Jesus
John 16 and
23 John 16 and
23 we are definitely in feedr John 16
and 23 go ahead in that day ye shall ask
me nothing very very I say unto you
whatsoever you shall ask the father in
my name he will give it you oh and we
know the son's name is Jesus also
anybody
else all right we'll leave it right
there and we'll move on to the next
question the next question is is there
any scriptures I can give that show why
we shouldn't wear a cross around our
necks why is it a bad idea to wear a
cross around our necks brother Julius
because the cross is they say it's a
symbol of uh Christ sacrifice no it is a
symbol a Roman symbol of capital
punishment and torture let's go to
Exodus the 20th chapter and we're going
to read verses 3 to five quickly
Jerome uh
tanzel Exodus 203 and5 all images are
not bad images but when you attribute
them to God you just crossed over into
idolatry Exodus 23 to five quickly thou
shall have no other gods before
me thou shall not make it to thee any
Graven image or any lik of anything that
is in heaven above or that is in the
earth beneath or that is in the water
under the Earth thou shall not bow down
thyself to them nor serve them for I the
Lord thy God am a jealous God visiting
the iniquities of the fathers upon the
children to the third and fourth
generation of them that hate me so they
say that I we a cross because Jesus died
on the cross but he never told you to
wear a cross look what he told you to do
let's go to Luke and the ninth chapter
Luke chapter 9 remember the Romans set
the cross up as an instrument of capital
punishment the book that the history
book tell you that the crosses was never
be crucifixion was not a new thing Rome
just came along and use it as a symbol
of capital punishment and
torture Luke 9 Luke
9:22 remember what we just read Luke
9:22 and we going to 24 go ahead saying
the son of man must suffer many things
and be rejected for the elders and chief
priests and scribes and be slained and
be raised the third day he was he he was
slain and they hung him on the cross he
suffered he was beaten he was uh thowing
pushed on his head continue and he said
unto them all if any man will come after
me let him deny himself and take up his
cross daily and follow me that's the
cook right there if you going to follow
Jesus you got to be willing to suffer
and even die for your faith and that's
what this is all about so the cross is
not a symbol of Christ uh sacrifice it
is a Roman instrument of Cruelty capital
punishment and torture that's why the
crosses that's why the that's how the
Romans killed people they would crucify
them on a cross and Rome got the whole
world wearing crosses
all right thank you for that brother
hope that answered their question there
sister Deborah one more question and
we're going to close out go ahead all
right uh Zion asked in Matthew 28 verse
19 is the Holy Ghost Nam Jesus also
since we have to be baptized in Jesus
name Matthew 28 verse verse 19 why don't
we go and read that and then brother
Julius I saw you um shaking your head so
we go give you the first crack Matthew
28:19 go ahead brother tanzel go ye
therefore and teach All Nations
baptizing them in the name of the father
and of the son and of the Holy Ghost
brother Julius and the Lord told you the
Holy Spirit whom I will send Luke uh
let's go to Luke uh I'm sorry uh St John
14 and 15
St John 14 and read verse
15 cuz he said gonna send the uh I want
that scripture where he say the Holy
Spirit who shall he shall send in his
name 26 uhhuh but the comforter which is
the Holy Ghost whom the father will send
in my name there you go so the father's
name is Jesus the son name was Jehovah
we can read that in Exodus the 6th
chapter and then he came in his father's
name if you read Luke the first chapter
the angel Gabriel will s to Mary and
told him you going to have a son you
should call his name Jesus and he shall
be called the son of the highest so the
father gave him his own name no other
name higher than Jesus and you are
baptized in the name of Jesus the angel
GNA come in the name of Jesus so that
one names uh the Holy Ghost is not Jesus
he's coming in the name of Jesus I hope
that
helped anybody here
good
enough all right good enough as my
brother said so sister Deborah time
check
902 902 well we want to thank everybody
from all around the world who tuned in
with us this evening thank you and if
you submitted a question last time and
we didn't get to it this week hey we
will address that question next week so
no need to Res subit your question we'll
get back to it but we want to say to
everybody who has joined us until we
come together again we ask you all to
please be safe be blessed stay prayerful
and may the Lord have mercy on us all as
brother tzel closes us
out Our Father which are in heaven
Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom come
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us of our debts as we
forgive our debtors and lead us not into
temptation but Deliver Us from Evil for
thine is the kingdom and the power and
the glory forever in Jesus name we pray
amen